<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Yoga</string>
    <string name="yoga">Yoga</string>
    <string name="hello">Hello</string>
    <string name="pranayama">Pranayama</string>
    <string name="welcome_to_pranayama">Welcome to pranayama</string>
    <string name="yoga_poses">Yoga poses</string>

<!--    <string name="bridge_desc">Yoga</string>-->
<!--    <string name="birdge_uses">Yoga</string>-->
<!--    -->



    <string name="bridge_desc">The bridge pose \n \n\nThe pose is entered from Sarvangasana or shoulderstand, the chest being held forwards by the hands and the feet lowered to the ground behind the back, the knees remaining bent; or more easily, by lifting the back from lying supine on the ground.</string>
    <string name="wheel_desc">The wheel pose \n\n\nIn the general form of the asana, the practitioner has hands and feet on the floor, and the abdomen arches up toward the sky.</string>
    <string name="tree_desc">The tree pose \n\n\n From Tadasana, weight is shifted to one leg, for example, starting with the left leg.\n The entire sole of the foot remains in contact with the floor.\n The right knee is bent and the right foot placed on the left inner thigh, or in half lotus position.\n In either foot placement, the hips should be open, with the bent knee pointing towards the side.\n With the toes of the right foot pointing directly down, the left foot, center of the pelvis, shoulders and head are all vertically aligned.\n Hands are typically held above the head either pointed directly upwards and unclasped, or clasped together in anjali mudra. The asana is typically held for 20 to 60 seconds, returning to tadasana while exhaling, then repeating standing on the opposite leg.</string>
    <string name="camel_desc">The camel pose \n\n\nUstrasana or Camel pose is a deep backward bend from a kneeling position; the completed pose has the hands on the heels. The backs of the feet may be flat on the floor, or the toes may be tucked under for a slightly less strong backbend.  </string>
    <string name="downward_desc">The downward pose \n\n\nThe pose has the head down, ultimately touching the floor, with the weight of the body on the palms and the feet. The arms are stretched straight forward, shoulder width apart; the feet are a foot apart, the legs are straight, and the hips are raised as high as possible.</string>
    <string name="warrior_desc">The warrior pose or Virabhadrasana \n\n\nstarting from Tadasana, the feet are spread wide, the front foot is turned fully out, and the back foot is turned in very slightly. \nThe body remains facing forwards, so the hips remain in line with the feet, the body sinks down into a lunge until the front knee is bent at a right angle, and the arms are extended fully with the palms down, at shoulder level. \nThe gaze is directed straight forward over the front hand </string>
    <string name="plow_desc">The plow pose\n\n\nThe pose is entered from Sarvangasana or shoulderstand, lowering the back slightly for balance, and moving the arms and legs over the head until the outstretched toes touch the ground and the fingertips, in a preparatory variant of the pose. \nThe arms may then be moved to support the back into a more vertical position, giving a second variant pose.\n Finally, the arms may be stretched out on the ground away from the feet, giving the final pose in the shape of a traditional plough</string>
    <string name="cobra_desc">The cobra pose\n\n\nThe pose may be entered from a prone position or from Downward Dog.\n The palms are placed under the shoulders, pushing down until the hips lift slightly. \nThe backs of the feet rest on the ground, the legs outstretched; the gaze is directed forwards, giving the preparatory pose. \nFor the full pose, the back is arched until the arms are straight, and the gaze is directed straight upwards or a little backwards. \nThe legs remain on the ground, unlike in the similar Upward Dog pose</string>
    <string name="dancer_desc">The dancer pose\n\n\nThe pose is entered from standing in Tadasana, bending one knee and stretching that foot back until it can be grasped with the hand on that side.\n The foot can then be extended back and up, arching the back and stretching out the other arm forwards.\nFor the full pose and a stronger stretch, reverse the rear arm by lifting it over the shoulder, and grasp the foot</string>
    <string name="elbow_desc">The elbow stand \n\n\nCome to your hands and knees facing the wall. \nYour fingertips should be pretty close to the wall. \nYour upper arms should be perpendicular to the forearms. \nYour gaze should be should be forward and down.\nCurl your toes under and lift your hips to come into a Downward Facing Dog or Adho Mukha Svanasana position with your legs.\nWalk your feet in toward your elbows as much as possible.\n Ideally, your hips will come over your shoulders.\nLift your dominant leg to a Down-Dog Split or Eka Pada Adho Mukha Svanasana position.\nExhale and bend the knee of the leg that is still on the floor.\n Kick the lifted leg with the foot flexed as your bottom leg hops up.\n Try to land both heels softly on the wall.\n Note that the head stays up off the floor. \nKeep your gaze on the floor between your hands.\nEngaging the core and hug the ribs in.\nIf you are able to get both legs up and invert fully, continue to work on engaging your core so you can remove your feet from the wall one at a time and balance independently.\n Remain in the pose one to five minutes, breathing slowly and deeply.\nCome down and rest </string>
    <string name="headstand_desc">The headstand \n\n\nGet on your hands and knees with your wrists under your shoulders and your knees under your hips.\nBring your forearms to the floor, keeping your elbows directly under your shoulders.\nClasp each hand around the opposite elbow. Adjust as needed to ensure your elbows are the right distance apart.\nRelease your hands from your elbows.\nClasp your hands together on the floor, interlacing your fingers .\nPlace the crown of your head on the floor. The very top of your head should be down—neither too far forward nor back. The back of your head will rest at the bases of your thumbs rather than your hands holding your skull.\nLift your hips and straighten your legs as if you were doing Downward-Facing Dog.\nCarefully walk your feet in toward your head until your hips are as close to over your shoulders as possible.\nNext is the trickiest part of the pose: lifting your feet off the floor. There are two methods that work best for beginners.</string>
    <string name="triangle_desc">The triangle\n\n\nBegin with both legs straight and about three feet apart.\n Your hips should be squared toward the front of your mat with your left foot stepped forward and your back foot turned out about forty five degrees.\nTake a deep breath. With your hands on your hips, hinge your torso forward over your front leg. \nKeep your spine straight.\n When you start to feel like your spine wants to round, back off slightly.\nExhale and pause here to decide which position will be most comfortable for your right hand.\n You can place it directly under your left shoulder, inside your left foot, or outside your left foot.\nInhale. \nPlace your left hand on your sacrum, feeling that it is level.\nExhale.\n Keep your hand in place as you twist your torso, opening your chest to the left. \nIf your sacrum begins to feel uneven, level it out by drawing your left hip forward and your right hip back.\nInhale as you lift your left hand toward the ceiling.\n Open your chest and stack your left shoulder over the right \nExhale smoothly and gaze up toward your right fingertips.\nHold this position for several deep breaths or up to one minute.\nWhen you are ready, exhale as you untwist and release.\nInhale and repeat on the other side, this time starting with the right food forward.</string>
    <string name="mermaid_desc">The mermaid \n\n\nBegin in Pigeon prep with your right leg forward.\nBend your back knee and grab hold of your left foot with your left hand.\nSlide your foot into the crook of your left elbow. \nYou can stop here or progress to the next step.Reach your right arm straight up toward the ceiling. \nBend your elbow, drop your right hand behind your head\nBring your hands to meet. \nPress the back of your head into your right arm.\nTry not to fall over onto the right side of your hip.\n Keep your chest pointing toward the front of your mat.\nRelease your foot, slowly lower your leg with control, and repeat the pose with the left knee forward.</string>

    <string name="warrior_uses">Strengthens your shoulders, arms, legs, ankles and back. \n Opens yours hips, chest and lungs. \n Improves focus, balance and stability.\nEncourages good circulation and respiration. \nStretches your arms, legs, shoulders, neck, belly, groins and ankles.\n Energizes the entire body.</string>
    <string name="bridge_uses">Stretches the chest, neck, and spine\nCalms the brain and helps alleviate stress and mild depression\n Stimulates abdominal organs, lungs, and thyroid\nRejuvenates tired legs\nImproves digestion\nHelps relieve the symptoms of menopause\nRelieves menstrual discomfort when done supported\nReduces anxiety, fatigue, backache, headache, and insomnia\nTherapeutic for asthma, high blood pressure, osteoporosis, and sinusitis</string>
    <string name="wheel_uses">It stretches and opens up the accessory muscles used in breathing. \n It strengthens the muscles of the shoulder girdle. \nIt stretches the hip flexors. \nIt\'s a great inversion. \nIt\'s a heart-opener, which helps us maintain emotional stability.</string>
    <string name="camel_uses">Stretches the entire front of the body, the ankles, thighs and groins,\nAbdomen and chest, and throat.\nStretches the deep hip flexors \nStrengthens back muscles.\nImproves posture.\nStimulates the organs of the abdomen and neck.</string>
    <string name="tree_uses">It strengthens the legs, and opens the hips.\nIt improves your neuromascular coordination.\nIt helps with balance and endurance.\nIt improves alertness and concentration.\nIt may help those who suffer from sciatica </string>
    <string name="downward_uses">Strengthens the whole body i.e upper body, arms, shoulders, abdomen and legs.\nStretches the back of the body, ankles, calves, hamstrings, spine.\nCalms the mind.\nStimulates blood circulation.\nDownward Dog is a great pose to rest the spine between strong backbends and forward bends.</string>
    <string name="plow_uses">Plow Pose opens the neck, shoulders, and back. By compressing the abdomen, it massages and tones the digestive organs, which improves detoxification. This pose stimulates and regulates the thyroid gland, relieves excess phlegm and mucus, and regulates the breath.</string>
    <string name="cobra_uses">Strengthens the spine.\nStretches chest and lungs, shoulders, and abdomen.\nTones the buttocks.\nStimulates abdominal organs.\nHelps relieve stress and fatigue.\nOpens the heart and lungs.\nSoothes sciatica.\nTherapeutic for asthma.</string>
    <string name="dancer_uses">It opens the shoulders, chest, and hips, as it stretches and strengthens the thighs, ankles, and abdomen. This pose develops greater flexibility in your spine, shoulders, and hamstrings. It also stretches the entire front of the body, while strengthening the back muscles, which improves posture</string>
    <string name="elbow_uses">The Forearm Stand strengthens the arms, shoulders, core, and back.\n Practicing it improves your balance and helps you overcome your fear of falling. \nAs an inversion, you will get increased blood flow to the brain, which may help relieve stress. \nIn yoga tradition, inversions open the third eye chakra to improve your mental abilities.</string>
    <string name="headstand_uses">When done with focus, strength, and care, headstands can be an invigorating part of your yoga practice. The pose requires skill and mental fortitude. It also develops your core strength and challenges your whole body—from your shoulders to your toes, helping you improve your balance.</string>
    <string name="mermaid_uses">This pose stretches the hips, quads, groin, and shoulders. It is also a backbend that opens the heart. In preparing for this pose, you will develop great flexibility in your hips, shoulders, and back. You will also challenge your balance. Practicing this pose will help you build even greater flexibility, which will help you throughout your daily life.</string>
    <string name="triangle_uses">With a combination of deep twisting, hamstring stretching, heart opening, and precarious balance, Revolved Triangle or Parivrtta Trikonasana is a challenging yoga pose for even experienced practitioners. Once you get the hang of it, though, Reversed Triangle has some excellent benefits that extend beyond your yoga practice into daily life by increasing flexibility and mobility, improving balance and core strength, opening the chest and shoulders, easing pain and other symptoms, and improving focus.</string>

    <!--        <string name="bridgep_desc">The bridge pose \n \n\nThe pose is entered from Sarvāṅgāsana (shoulderstand), the chest being held forwards by the hands and the feet lowered to the ground behind the back, the knees remaining bent; or more easily, by lifting the back from lying supine on the ground.</string>-->
    <!--        <string name="warriorp_desc">Bhastrika Pranayam \n Bhastrika Pranayam is also known as Bellows Breath. In this breath yoga, a sound like a blacksmith bellows is produced. According to Yoga Guru Baba Ramdev, Bhastrika pranayama is done first on breath yoga series. </string>-->
       <string name="kapalbhati_pranayama">Kapalbhati Pranayama \n According to some yogis it a purification technique that is why it is known as Skull Purification. In Kapalbhati Pranayam we have to blow the air out from out both nostrils by which our stomach naturally goes inside.</string>-->
    <!--    <string name="camelp_desc">Bahya Pranayama \n Bahya Pranayama or Tri Bandha Or Maha Bandha is a combination of 3 bandha i.e Mula Bandha, Jalandhara Bandha, and Uddiyana Bandha. This pranayama is very beneficial for stomach related disorders.</string>-->
        <string name="anulom_vilom_pranayam">Anulom Vilom Pranayam \n Anulom Vilom is also known as Alternate Nostril breathing which is a nerve purification breath yoga. By using our right hand we breathe in and out from our both nostrils one by one.</string>
    <!--    <string name="wheelp_desc">Bhramari Pranayam \n In Bharamari Pranayam we have to make a sound like a bee. The Bhramari word is derived from the Sanskrit language. The vibration produced by this pranayama is very beneficial for mental illness and heart blockages.</string>-->
    <!--    <string name="Udgeeth Pranayama">Udgeeth Pranayama \n Udgeeth Pranayam or Omkar Chanting is pranayama which takes us to the state of meditation. In this pranayama, we take a long deep breath and then chant Om. The vibrations of AUM calm our mind and take us to the meditative state.</string>-->
    <!--    <string name="Shitali Pranayama">Shitali Pranayama \n Softly Pranayama is the best yoga for summer. Through this pranayama, we can control the temperature of our body. You have to make a shape like a pipe from your tongue and then breathe in with the pipe. After holding the breath in for a while, the breath has to be left out from the nostrils.</string>-->
    <!--    <string name="Sheetkari Pranayama">Sheetkari Pranayama \n Sheetkari pranayama is similar to that of pranayama. Benefits from both pranayamas are also almost the same. The only difference between them is that in Sitali Pranayam we roll our tongue but in Sheetkari we connect our upper and lower teeth and then take a breath.</string>-->
        <string name="nadi_shuddhi_pranayam">Nadi Shuddhi Pranayam \n Nadi Shodhan Pranayama means Alternate nostril breathing. The primary benefit of Nadi Shuddhi is cleansing of the nerves. There is a little difference in the practice of Nadi Shuddhi and Anulom Vilom but the benefits of both are almost the same.</string>
    <!--  <string name="Ujjayi Pranayam">Ujjayi Pranayam \n This pranayama is considered to be the best pranayama for thyroid patient. When practicing this pranayama, the vibration that is produced by our throats makes a special effect on the throat and thyroid gland.</string>-->
    <!--    <string name="Vritti Pranayama">Vritti Pranayama \n Vritti Pranayama is of two types – Sama Vritti Pranayama and Vishama Vritti Pranayama. The breathing ratio is similar in the Sama Vritti Pranayama, whereas, in Vishama Vritti Pranayama, the breathing ratio is irregular.</string>-->
    <!--    <string name="Surya Bhedana Pranayama">Surya Bhedana Pranayama \n In Yoga, our right nostril is related to the sun and the left nostril is related to the moon. Therefore, In Surya Bhedna Pranayama we only breathe from the right nostril and only leave the breath out from the left nostril.</string>-->
    <!--    <string name="Chandra Bhedana Pranayam">Chandra Bhedana Pranayam \n In Chandra Bhedna Pranayama we only breathe in from the left nostril and leave the breath out from right nostril.</string>-->
    <!--    <string name="Palvini Pranayam">Palvini Pranayam \n Palvini is a Sanskrit word which means swim. If you want to practice this pranayama then you need to know other pranayamas also. In simple language, this pranayama is not for beginners. In this breath yoga, breathing is held according to desire.</string>-->
    <!--    <string name="Murcha Pranayama">Murcha Pranayama \n Moorcha is a Sanskrit word which means suspension from all the mental activities. This pranayama is also difficult to do for beginners. This breath yoga keeps you away from stress, anxiety, depression, and all mental disorders.</string>-->

    <string name="warriorp_uses">Strengthens your shoulders, arms, legs, ankles and back. \n Opens yours hips, chest and lungs. \n Improves focus, balance and stability.\nEncourages good circulation and respiration. \nStretches your arms, legs, shoulders, neck, belly, groins and ankles.\n Energizes the entire body.</string>
    <string name="treep_uses">It strengthens the legs, and opens the hips.\nIt improves your neuromascular coordination.\nIt helps with balance and endurance.\nIt improves alertness and concentration.\nIt may help those who suffer from sciatica (nerve pain in the leg)</string>
    <string name="downwardp_uses">Strength</string>
</resources>